Guide to the Ken Kennedy academic records, 1967-2007 MS 206
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Academic papers, presentations, books and slides, 1971-2006 (Boxes 52-60)
  - Complexity of Interprocedural Side-Effect Analysis. October 1987. (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - A Practical Environment for Scientific Programming. November 1987. (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - ParaScope Newsletter #8: Proposed Changes to the Composition Editor. 1988 January 27 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - PTOOL: A System for Static Analysis of Parallel Programs. 1988 March 12. (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Estimating Interlock and Improving Balance for Pipeline Architectures. August 1988. (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - ParaScope: A Parallel Programming Environment. September 1988. (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Compiling Programs for Distributed-Memory Multiprocessors. October 1988. (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Analysis of Interprocedural Side Effects in a Parallel Programming Environment. 1988. (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Fast Interprocedural Alias Analysis. January 1989. (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Virtual Shared Memory for Distributed-Memory Machines. March 1989. (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Compiling for Distributed-Memory Machines: Proposal for a Tutorial. 1989 May 25. (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - ParaScope Newsletter #?: Summer 1989 Research Goals. 1989 June 6. (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Interprocedural Analysis and Optimization. 1989 June 18. (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - A Dynamic Study of Vectorization in PFC. 1989 July 10. (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Dependence-based Register Allocation. 1989 July 19. (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - A Technique for Summarizing Data Access and Its Use in Parallelism Enhancing Transformations. July 1989. (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Constructing the Procedure Call Multigraph. 1989 September 6. (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - Analyzing and Visualizing Performance of Memory Hierarchies. 1989 October 20. (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - An Algorithm for Call Multigraph Construction. 1989 November 9 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - The ParaScope Editor: An Interactive Parallel Programming Tool. November 1989. (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Blocking Linear Algebra Codes for Memory Hierarchies. December 1989. (Box 53, Folder 43)
  - Compile-time Detection of Race Conditions in a Parallel Program. 1989. (Box 53, Folder 44)
  - Improving Loop Balance. 1989. (Box 53, Folder 45)
  - Performance of parallel processors. 1989. (Box 53, Folder 46)
  - Software Prefetching. 1990 March 30. (Box 53, Folder 47)
  - An Interactive Environment for Data Partitioning and Distribution. April 1990 (Box 53, Folder 48)
  - Improving Register Allocation for Subscripted Variables. June 1990. (Box 53, Folder 49)
  - Software for Supercomputers of the Future. 1990 July 19. (Box 53, Folder 50)
  - Interprocedural Optimization: Eliminating unnecessary Recompilation. 1990 July 30 (Box 53, Folder 51)
  - Experience with Interprocedural Analysis of Array Side Effects. 1990 September 29. (Box 53, Folder 52)
  - Parallel Program Debugging with the On-the-fly Anomaly Detection. November 1990. (Box 53, Folder 53)
  - Fortran D Language Specification. December, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 54)
  - Compiling Scientific Code for Complex Memory Hierarchies. January 1991. (Box 53, Folder 55)
  - An Implementation of Interprocedural Bounded Regular Section Analysis. 1991 March 22. (Box 53, Folder 56)
  - Compiler Optimizations for Fortran D on MIMD Distributed-Memory Machines. April 1991. (Box 53, Folder 57)
  - Analysis and Transformation in the ParaScope Editor. June 1991. (Box 53, Folder 58)
  - Interactive Parallel Programming Using the ParaScope Editor. July 1991. (Box 53, Folder 59)
  - A Static Performance Estimator to Guide Data Partitioning Decisions. July 1991 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Interprocedural Compilation of Fortran D for MIMD Distributed-Memory Machines. November 1991. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - An Overview of the Fortran D Programming System. 1991 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Evaluating Parallel Languages for Molecular Dynamics Computations. 1992 April 26-29. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Optimizing for Parallelism and Data Locality. April 1992. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Procedure Cooling. April 1992. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Relaxing SIMD Control Flow Constraints using Loop Transformations. April 1992. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Simple Models for Parallel Computation. 1992 June 2. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Compiler Analysis for Irregular Problems in Fortran D. June 1992 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Software Support for Irregular and Loosely Synchronous Problems. June 1992. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Vector Register Allocation. October 1992. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Solving Integer Programs from Dependence and Synchronization Problems. 1992. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - A Static Performance Estimator in the Fortran D Programming System. 1992. (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Automatic Data Layout for Distributed-Memory Machines in the D Programming Environment. February 1993. (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - The ParaScope Parallel Programming Environment. February 1993. (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - A Methodology for Procedure Cloning. April, 1993. (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Experiences Using the ParaScope Editor: an Interactive Parallel Programming Tool. May 1993. (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Compiler Technology for Machine-Independent Parallel Programming. 1993 June 21. (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Initial Framework for Automatic Data Layout in Fortran D: A Short Update on a Case Study. July 1993 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Analysis and transformation in an interactive parallel programming tool. October 1993. (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Multi-processor Cluster Computing, A Research Infrastructure Proposal to the National Science Foundation. October, 1993. (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - A Vision Statement for the D System. 1993 December 8. (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Unified Compilation of Fortran 77D and 90D. 1993. (Box 54, Folder 23)
  - Languages, Compilers, and Runtime Systems Support for Parallel Input-Output. January, 1994. (Box 54, Folder 24)
  - Scalar Replacement in the Presence of Conditional Control Flow. January 1994. (Box 54, Folder 25)
  - Typed Fusion with Applications to Parallel and Sequential Code Generation. January 1994. (Box 54, Folder 26)
  - The D System: Support for Data-Parallel Programming. 1994 March 9. (Box 54, Folder 27)
  - GIVE-N-TAKE- A Balanced Code Placement Framework. March, 1994. (Box 54, Folder 28)
  - Evaluating Compiler Optimizations for Fortran D. April 1994. (Box 54, Folder 29)
  - Automatic Data Layout Using 0-1 Integer Programming. August 1994. (Box 54, Folder 30)
  - An Algorithm for Minimizing Spill Code in Loops. 1994 October 20. (Box 54, Folder 31)
  - The D Editor: A New Interactive Parallel Programming Tool. November 1994. (Box 54, Folder 32)
  - Improving the Ratio of Memory Operations to Floating-Point Operations in Loops. November 1994. (Box 54, Folder 33)
  - Minimizing Spill Code in Loop-Contained Basic Blocks. 1994. (Box 54, Folder 34)
  - A Research Agenda for High Performance Computing Software. 1994. (Box 54, Folder 35)
  - Value-Based Distributions in Fortran D. 1994. (Box 54, Folder 36)
  - A Constraint Based Communication Placement Framework. February 1995. (Box 54, Folder 37)
  - An Empirical Study of Cross-Loop Reuse in the NAS Benchmarks. March 1995. (Box 54, Folder 38)
  - A Method for Optimal Register Allocation to Loops in Multiple Register File Architectures. June, 1995. (Box 54, Folder 39)
  - Efficient Address Generation for Block-Cyclic Distributions. July 1995. (Box 54, Folder 40)
  - A Linear-Time Algorithm for Computing the Memory Access Sequence in Data-Parallel Programs. July 1995. (Box 54, Folder 41)
  - Index Array Flattening Through Program Transformation. August 1995. (Box 54, Folder 42)
  - A Model and Compilation Strategy for Out-of-Core Data Parallel Programs. August, 1995. (Box 54, Folder 43)
  - Optimizing Fortran 90 Shift Operations on Distributed-Memory Multicomputers. August 1995. (Box 54, Folder 44)
  - Interprocedural Array Side Effect Analysis. 1995 September 9. (Box 54, Folder 45)
  - Optimal Register Assignment to Loops for Embedded Code Generation. September 1995. (Box 54, Folder 46)
  - An Integrated Compilation and Performance Analysis Environment for Data Parallel Programs. October 1995. (Box 54, Folder 47)
  - Automatic Data Layout for High Performance Fortran. December 1995. (Box 54, Folder 48)
  - Communication Generation for Cyclic (K) Distributions. 1995. (Box 54, Folder 49)
  - Efficient Call Graph Analysis. March 1996. (Box 54, Folder 50)
  - A Method for Register Allocation to Loops in Multiple Register File Architectures. April, 1996. (Box 54, Folder 51)
  - Compiler Techniques for Software Prefetching on Cache-Coherent Shared Memory Multiprocessors. June 1996. (Box 54, Folder 52)
  - Dependence Analysis of Fortran 90 Array Syntax. 1996 August 9-11. (Box 54, Folder 53)
  - Cross-loop Reuse Analysis and its Application to Cache Optimizations. August 1996. (Box 54, Folder 54)
  - Resource-Based Communication Placement Analysis. August 1996. (Box 54, Folder 55)
  - Interprocedural Compilation of Fortran D. November 1996 (Box 54, Folder 56)
  - A Communication Placement Framework with Unified Dependence and Data-flow Analysis. 1996. (Box 54, Folder 57)
  - Experiences in Data-Parallel Programming. 1997. (Box 54, Folder 58)
  - Automatic Data Layout for Distributed Memory Machines. July 1998. (Box 54, Folder 59)
  - Optimizing Strategies for Telescoping Languages: Procedure Strength Reduction and Procedure Vectorization. June 2001. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Fast Greedy Weighted Fusion. October 2001. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - An Approximate Balancing Algorithm for Efficient Broadcast. 2001 September 18. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - What Are the Top Ten Most Influential Parallel and Distributed Processing Concepts of the Past Millennium? December 2001. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Telescoping Languages: A Strategy for Automatic Generation of Scientific Problem-Solving Systems from Annotated Libraries. 2001. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Reducing and Vectorizing Procedures for Telescoping Languages. August 2002. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Vizer: A System to Vectorize Intel x86 Binaries. 2002 October 14-15. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - High-Level Optimization of S Language Programs. 2002. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - KELPIO: a telescope-ready domain-specific I/O library for irregular block- structured applications. 2002 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Optimizing Compilers for Modern Architectures. 2002. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Special Issue: High Performance Fortran. 2002. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Languages, Compilers, and Run-Time Systems. Fall 2003. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Improving Memory Hierarchy Performance through Combined Loop Interchange and Multi-Level Fusion. May 2004. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Automatic Blocking of QR and LU Factorizations for Locality. June 2004. (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - An Automatic Source-level Transformer for Improving the Performance of DSP Applications in MATLAB. August 2004. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Defining and Measuring the Productivity of Programming Languages. Winter 2004. (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Improving Effective Bandwidth through Compiler Enhancement of Global Cache Reuse. 2004. (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Transforming Complex Loop Nests for Locality. 2004. (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Scalarization using Loop Alignment and Loop Skewing. January 2005. (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Telescoping Languages: A System for Automatic Generation of Domain Languages. February 2005. (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Task Scheduling Strategies for Workflow-Based Applications in Grids. May 2005. (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - New Grid Scheduling and Rescheduling Methods in the GrADS Project. June 2005. (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - NEC SX-4 (Slides) (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Dept. Research Talk (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Computer Science Overview May 1991 Affiliates (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Affiliates 1992 (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - High-Level Programming Systems (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - CRPC Slides (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - CRPC Affiliates Talk (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Debugging Conference Keynote (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - SHPCC Tutorial (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Software Support for Parallel Programming (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Parallel Prog. Environment (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Provost Lecture (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Owlnet Overview (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Parasol Slides (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Corky's Parasol Overview (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Overview for CER Site Visit (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - CER Overview (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - America Online - Hawk's Key Seminar (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Owlnet Slides (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Newport Workshop on Supercomputing (Admirals, etc.) (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Alumni Lecture (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - CRPC Programming Env. for Parallel Computing Tutorial (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Exxon Talk (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Siemens Talk (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Older Parallel Software Support Talk (Xerox only) (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Miscellaneous ParaScope (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - ParaScope Workshop July 1991 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - ParaScope Slides (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous Parallel Processors (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Current Parallel Slides (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Parallel Code Generation (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Loop Interchange (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - Parallel Program Debugging with On-the-fly Anomaly Detection by R. Hood/K. Kennedy/J. Mellor-Crummey (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - Siemens Parallel Debug Aug. 6, 1990 (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - Slides for Debugging Keynote (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - ParaScope Debug Slides (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - Intro Parallelism Lecture (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - CDC Executive Seminar - 35 minutes (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - Environment Slides (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - Environment Originals (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Programming Environment (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - Notes from Palo Alto (Box 55, Folder 64)
  - Kennedy GCC Talk (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - H Flatt Materials (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Petaflops Architectures (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - IT Venture Forum 2005 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Working Group 2.11 Invited Talk. 6-9 March 2005 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Wiley Copyright Transfer Agreement 1995 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - ICASE Fortran D (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Loveman Slides (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Academic Papers, 1994 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Salzburg Fortran D. 30 Sept 1991 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - HPC SW Talk (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - CRPC Fortran Overview (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Fortran D Optimization (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Distribution Memory Extra Slides (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Parallel Computation Slides (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Fortran D Compiler and HPF (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - SC91-Compilation Intro Dependence and Parallelization (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - SC91 Tutorial: Interprocedural Arial (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Machine-Independent Evaluation of Parallelizing Compilers - Petersen/Padua (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Politically Incorrect Fortran (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - SIO Overview (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Cancun Papers (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Priority Reading (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Java Papers (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - The Technology Behind Crusoe Processors (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Programming Articles (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Emotion Engino et al (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Keshav Pingali (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Give N Take (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - The Silk Road Project. 10 Dec 1999 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Java ITR Proposal (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Script ITR Proposal (Box 56, Folder 32)
  - Java Reading (Box 56, Folder 33)
  - Talks/Abstracts (Box 56, Folder 34)
  - A Rice Perspective on Software Engineering Licensing by Kennedy and Vardi Aug 2002 (Box 56, Folder 35)
  - Supercomputing Papers (Box 56, Folder 36)
  - ACM - Publications, Papers, etc. (Box 56, Folder 37)
  - Financial Disclosure (Box 56, Folder 38)
  - IEEE Copyright. April 2, 2000 (Box 56, Folder 39)
  - 20 Years of the ACM/Sigplan Conference (Box 56, Folder 40)
  - ACM Copyright Form Fast Copy - Coalescing and Live Range Identification (Box 56, Folder 41)
  - Journal Proofs - CPE 696 (Box 56, Folder 42)
  - HUG Special Issue Wiley Publishers Transmission From 2001 (Box 56, Folder 43)
  - SIO Book Author's Letter of Agreement (CTA Form) 2002 (Box 56, Folder 44)
  - Copyright Agreements 2001 (Box 56, Folder 45)
  - Special Issue of IJPP CTA and Disk Description Forms (Box 56, Folder 46)
  - Papers (Various) (Box 56, Folder 47)
  - Time Skewing (Box 56, Folder 48)
  - Qing Paper 24 October 2001 (Box 56, Folder 49)
  - Ossoda RFI Response (Box 56, Folder 50)
  - Compiler Techniques for High-Performance Computing with Java 2005 (Box 56, Folder 51)
  - Policy Reading (Box 56, Folder 52)
  - Anirban Broadcast Reading (Box 56, Folder 53)
  - IA-64 Compilation (Box 56, Folder 54)
  - TJs Reviews on Paper "Scalarization using Loop Alignment and Loop Skewing" (Box 56, Folder 55)
  - Fusion References (Box 56, Folder 56)
  - Journals - Top 10 References (Box 56, Folder 57)
  - High Performance Computing: Crays, Clusters, and Centers. What Next? (Box 56, Folder 58)
  - Scheduling Workflow Applications in GrADS Nov 2003 (Box 56, Folder 59)
  - GrADSoft and its Application Manager - Simplifying Using the Grid (Box 56, Folder 60)
  - LACSI Slides (Box 56, Folder 61)
  - Interprocedural Analysis and Optimization (Box 56, Folder 62)
  - Vector Register Allocation (2f) (Box 56, Folder 63-64)
  - Miscellaneous Academic Papers (Box 56, Folder 65)
  - MPP Fortran Programming Model. 4 March 1992 (Box 56, Folder 66)
  - Compiler Support for Out-of-Core Data Structures on Parallel Machines (Box 56, Folder 67)
  - "Compilation for Software Distributed-Shared Memory Systems" thesis by Kai Zhang. June 1999 (Box 56, Folder 68)
  - Misc. Drafts, papers, correspondence, presentations (Box 56, Folder 69)
  - International Journal of Parallel Programming, Vol. 29, No.5, Oct 2001 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - IEEE - Constructing the Procedure Call Multigraph (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Illinois Vectorizer Documentation (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Vectranslator Document (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - George's Vectranslation Slides (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Argonne Transparencies (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Standardization/Prelim X forms (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Parallel Code Generation (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Originals (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Constant Propagation (Sigplan) (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Intro to Dependence (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Dependence Testing Talk (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Dependence Lecture (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Simple Dependence Testing (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Dependence Analysis (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Dependence Analysis Symposium (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Dependence Testing Sigplan (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Multiple Subscripts (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Recurrence Breaking (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Vector Register Allocation (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Optimization Bibliography (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - One-Cost Loop Work Rough Draft (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - GE Talk 1992 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Intel Talk (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Silicon Graphics Talk (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Rochester-Kodak Talk (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Challenges for Compilers (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Frontiers Talk (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Compiling for Distrib Memory (Box 57, Folder 29)
  - Distributed Memory Compilation (Box 57, Folder 30)
  - DMCC5 Tutorial (Box 57, Folder 31)
  - SC91: Introduction Architecture, Programming (Box 57, Folder 32)
  - Shell Talk (Box 57, Folder 33)
  - Chau-Wen's Distributed Memory Talk (Box 57, Folder 34)
  - Intel Touchstone Vienna (Box 57, Folder 35)
  - Machine Independent Programming (Item not specified, Box 57, Folder 36)
  - Machine Independent Parallel Programming (Box 57, Folder 37)
  - Portable Programming: Navy Workshop (Box 57, Folder 38)
  - Chau-Wen Slides (Box 57, Folder 39)
  - Distributed Memory New Slides (Box 57, Folder 40)
  - Distributed Memory Talk (Box 57, Folder 41)
  - Side Effects and Aliases (Box 57, Folder 42)
  - Interprocedural Analysis in a Parallel Programming Environment (Box 57, Folder 43)
  - Alias Analysis (Box 57, Folder 44)
  - Convex Luncheon Talk (Box 57, Folder 45)
  - Regular Sections (Box 57, Folder 46)
  - Convex Applications Compiler (Box 57, Folder 47)
  - Superscalar Optimization (Box 57, Folder 48)
  - Superscalar Optimization (Israel) (Box 57, Folder 49)
  - i860 Talk (Box 57, Folder 50)
  - CM-2 Lecture (Memory Hierarchy) (Box 57, Folder 51)
  - Complex Memory Hierarchy IBM Oberlech (Box 57, Folder 52)
  - Porterfield/Carr Slides (Box 57, Folder 53)
  - Complex Memory Hierarchy FPS Talk (Box 57, Folder 54)
  - Paper Draft: Combining Loop Fusion and Tiling for Improved Memory Performance (Box 57, Folder 55)
  - Various Academic Papers (Box 57, Folder 56)
  - Supercomputing Article/Editorial (Box 57, Folder 57)
  - Article on CRPC for IJ Supercomputer Applications (Box 57, Folder 58)
  - Sigplan RSD Submission (Box 57, Folder 59)
  - Article for Padua (Box 57, Folder 60)
  - CACM Paper with Tseng and Hiranandani (Box 57, Folder 61)
  - Chapter 6 first half (Box 57, Folder 62)
  - Book Outline (Box 57, Folder 63)
  - Book (Box 57, Folder 64)
  - Paper Submitted to CC 2004 "Specialization Engine…" October 2003 (Box 57, Folder 65)
  - Paper Submitted to CC 2004 "Scheduling Workflow Applications inGrADS (Box 57, Folder 66)
  - Grandinetti/Cetraro w/s book (Box 57, Folder 67)
  - Comments on Survey Papers (Box 57, Folder 68)
  - Keith's Comments (Box 57, Folder 69)
  - IPOPT Paper with Mauf, Kats, SC91 (Box 57, Folder 70)
  - Joint Optimization Paper with Fran (Box 57, Folder 71)
  - PTOOL Paper (Box 57, Folder 72)
  - ACPC Abstract Fortran D (Box 57, Folder 73)
  - Wiley Interscience (Box 57, Folder 74)
  - Ken Kennedy CV (Box 57, Folder 75)
  - Sid Fernbach (Ken's papers) (Box 57, Folder 76)
  - Automatic Translation of Fortran Programs to Vector Form. By Randy Allen and Ken Kennedy. July 1984 (Box 57, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence regarding Various Publications (Box 57, Folder 78)
  - Pearson Education Royalty Statement 1999 (Box 57, Folder 79)
  - Prentice-Hall Correspondence 1990 (Box 57, Folder 80)
  - Kennedy Foreword for Supercomputers for Parallel and Vector Computers. 1990 (Box 57, Folder 81)
  - Addison-Wesley (Box 57, Folder 82)
  - Copyright: Paper 8465 (Allen/Kennedy) Vector Register Allocation (2f) (Box 57, Folder 83-84)
  - ACM Revisions/Correspondence (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Kansas Survey (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Jones and Bartlett Contract 1992 (Tseng/Hiranandani/Kennedy) (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Jones and Bartlett (Carl Hessler) (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Compilation for Vector and Parallel Computers Book Outline (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Morgan Kaufmann Publishers (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Morgan Kaufmann Letter regarding Book Cover. 2 Aug 2001 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Kennedy Book Materials (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Book Review by Kathryn McKinley (2f) (Box 58, Folder 9-10)
  - Book Revisions by Randy Allen. 24 June 2001 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Book Revisions (2f) (Box 58, Folder 12-13)
  - Book Draft/Revisions. 10 Feb 2001. (2f) (Box 58, Folder 14-15)
  - Book Chapter Drafts/Revisions. Feb-April 2001. (3f) (Box 58, Folder 16-18)
  - Book Draft. 11 Jan 2001 (2f) (Box 58, Folder 19-20)
  - CRPC Book Kennedy (miscellaneous edits) (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Chapter 1 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Chapter 2 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Chapter 3 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Chapter 4 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Chapter 5 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Chapter 6 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Chapter 7 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Chapter 8 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Chapter 9 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Chapter 10 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Chapter 11 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Chapter 12 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Chapter 13 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Chapter 14 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Chapter 15 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Chapter 16 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Chapter 17 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Chapter 18 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Chapter 19 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Chapter 20 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Chapter 21 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Chapter 22 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Chapter 23 (Box 59, Folder 24)